shipbob.com 2019-06-04

# Privacy Policy - ShipBob

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.shipbob.com and ShipBob,Inc. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to ShipBob,Inc. include www.shipbob.com and ShipBob. The ShipBob website is a Packing and Shipping Services site. By using the ShipBob website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

### Collection of your Personal Information

ShipBob may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase ShipBob’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by ShipBob. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the ShipBob website.

ShipBob encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from ShipBob so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. ShipBob is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the ShipBob website.

### Use of your Personal Information

ShipBob collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

ShipBob may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from ShipBob and its affiliates. ShipBob may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

ShipBob does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

ShipBob may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. ShipBob may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to ShipBob, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

ShipBob may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within ShipBob, in order to determine what ShipBob services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within ShipBob to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

As you browse Shipbob.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with [company website]. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can visit this page (http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out of AdRoll and their partners’ targeted advertising.

ShipBob will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on ShipBob or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of ShipBob; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of ShipBob, or the public.

### Security of your Personal Information

ShipBob secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

### Children Under Thirteen

ShipBob does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

### Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from ShipBob by contacting us here:

  * Web page: [www.shipbob.com](https://www.shipbob.com/)
  * Email: [hello@shipbob.com](mailto:hello@shipbob.com)
  * Phone: (844) 474-4726

### Changes to this Statement

ShipBob will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. ShipBob encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how ShipBob is protecting your information.

### Contact Information

ShipBob welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that ShipBob has not adhered to this Statement, please contact ShipBob at:

**ShipBob,Inc.**  
120 N. Racine Ave #100  
Chicago, IL  
60607

**Email Address:**  

**Telephone number:**  
(844) 474-4726

Effective as of June 29, 2014  
Most recently updated on May 25, 2018
